暂时停职
Temporary suspension.
我的课怎么办
My classes?
- 你不被允许进入校园 - 什么
- You're not allowed on campus. - What?
他们必须给学生一个交代
They had to give something to the students,
尤其在与校警发生争执后
especially after the altercation with campus police.
拉森让他们为一个该死的捐赠者活动清理广场
Larson asked them to clear the quad for a fucking donor event.
因为那个大嘴巴
Because of that windbag,
我才和校警有过结的
I'm getting lumped in with campus police?
这太不公平了 都是因为他 你查清楚了吗
That's completely unfair. That's on him. Did you make that clear?
- 你帮我说话了吗 - 你没有...
- Did you defend me? - You don't...
你知道我都经历了些什么吗
Do you know what I've been dealing with?
学生来找我 和我哭诉...
Students coming and crying and...
这不是我作为主任想看到的
This isn't what I wanna be dealing with as chair.
我该怎么做呢
What should I do?
你需要做一个正式的道歉
You're going to need to formally apologize.
抱歉 我...
I'm so sorry. I...
不 不是对我说 笨蛋
No, not to me, dumbass!
我的意思是没错 要对我说
I mean yes, to me,
但他们正在组织一个纪律听证会
but they're putting together a disciplinary hearing,
你必须作出能让所有学生都接受的道歉
and you have to write an apology that can be disseminated.
天啊 什么
Jesus. What is...
是珠珠的学校 是在逗我呢吧 等我会
It's Ju Ju's school. You gotta be kidding me. Hold on.
你好
Hello.
是的 是我
Yes, this is she.
等会 打人还是咬人
Wait, hit or bit?
英文系主任 第一季 第04集
你们两个都被禁足了
You're both suspended.
我要去上班了 你们必须写检讨书
I'm going to work, and you are going to write letters.
珠珠 你需要向亚丁道歉
Ju Ju, you will apologize to Adin.
比尔 你需要向所有人道歉
Bill, you will apologize... to everyone.
那我整晚都得呆在这里了
Mmm. I'm gonna be here all night.
下节课 每个人都需要完成
For next time, everyone needs to come
宽恕者的传说
having finished "The Pardoner's Tale."
英国诗人乔叟所著的《坎特伯雷故事集》中的一个故事
讲述了贪婪与死亡
不能原谅偷懒者
No pardons for slackers.
嗨
Oh hi.
我们之前提过的那件事我搞定了
I was able to do that thing we talked about.
我不认为你真的...
I didn't think you were really...
我当时是在开玩笑
I was joking.
我认为你假装在开玩笑 但实际上你是认真的
I thought you were pretending to joke but were actually serious.
幸好我没有开玩笑说要杀了他
Good thing I didn't joke we should kill him.
- 好吧 - 所以你找到他了吗
- All right. - So you tracked him down?
不太确定 但是我
Not exactly. But I was able
侵入了教授评价网站
to hack into the Rate My Professor website.
侵入 不
Hack? No, I can't even be tangentially connected
我不能与任何不正当或违法的行为有关联
to anything that might seem improper conduct or illegal.
- 但是你想知道它是谁吗 - 当然
- But you wanna know who it is? - Yes.
好了
Okay.
两次的邮件都从人文图书馆发出
It was posted twice from the Humanities Library,
时间是下午五点至六点之间
both times between 5:00 p.M. And 6:00 p.M.
定位在二三三这个教室吗
Eff This Class223?
不是 是一个邮箱地址
No, EatMeChaucer@gmail.Com.
如果他再次发邮件
If he posts again, and, say,
我们也在图书馆的话...
we were at the library...
我的意思是 你就能找出那个人
Yeah. I mean, you'd have to recognize the guy.
那应该不会太难
That shouldn't be too hard.
如果抓住他的话 你想做什么
What are you gonna do if you catch him?
"毁灭他" 琼开玩笑地说
"Destroy him," Joan said jokingly,
当这刚好成为她计划做的事时
when that's exactly what she was planning to do.
嗨 我是来自彭布罗克校报的夏洛特・罗
Hi, I'm Charlotte Lo from The Pembroke Daily.
- 我给你留了言 - 是的 嗨
- I left you a few messages. - Right. Hi.
我不想评论整件事 好吗
Uh, I... I don't wanna comment on the whole thing, okay?
你站哪边呢 你会参加明天的抗议吗
Well, where do you stand? Are you joining the protest tomorrow?
我想人们会很乐意听到你的观点
I think people would appreciate hearing your point of view.
抱歉
Sorry.
是什么让你选择成为比尔・多布森的助教
What made you pursue Bill Dobson as a mentor in the first place?
我没法回答你 好吗
I... I can't answer, okay?
我们系的主任
The chair of my department gave me an earful
让我们不要和任何人谈论此事
about not talking to anyone about this.
- 天啊 - 她不做饭
- Jesus. - She doesn't cook.
现成午饭
- 我可以给你做些鸡蛋 - 我不吃鸡蛋
- I guess I'm making you some eggs, then. - I don't eat eggs.
你不喜欢吃鸡蛋 还是你从未尝试过
Because you don't like 'em, or you never tried 'em?
两个都有
Both.
如果你愿意尝一口 我就给你一美元
I'll give you a dollar if you try a bite.
说一样你能用一美元买到的东西吧
Name one thing you can buy with a dollar.
葡萄干
Raisins?
请进
Come in.
金教授 你有时间吗
Uh, Professor Kim, you got a sec?
当然 请进 达斯汀
Sure thing. Come in, Dustin.
你好 卡普里
Oh, hi, Capri.
请坐
Take a seat.
我们不坐了
We're okay.
怎么了
What's up?
政治科学系刚刚拒绝了他们系里
Poli Sci just denied tenure
唯一的有色人种的终身任职
to the only person of color in their department.
我们很担心麦凯教授
We're worried about Professor McKay.
他们是保守的老混蛋
They're conservative assholes.
黑人职员被用不同的标准来对待
Black faculty are held to different standards.
我知道
I know.
他们的研究根本不被认真对待
Their research isn't considered rigorous.
他们被认定为是不守规矩的 不合群的
They're assumed to be more disorganized, less collegial.
- 我知道 - 他们很少被邀请到
- I know. - They get invited less often
同事家里吃饭
to their colleagues' houses for dinner.
我知道
I know.
相信我 我真的知道
Trust me, I know.
这是三百二十个学生联合签名的信
This is a letter signed by 320 students
关于麦凯教授所受到的影响
about the impact Professor McKay has had.
也关于她支持有色人种学生的做法
The way she's supported students of color.
如果她的终身教职被拒绝了
If she is denied tenure,
我们会采取行动的
we plan to take action.
你看起来不太高兴啊
Don't you look dashing.
我瘦了一些 所以我需要把衣服改小一点
I lost a little weight, so I had this taken in,
但你看看他们都做了什么
but look what they did to the sleeves.
我是说 这袖子不是钟形的 这是椭圆形的
I mean, this isn't bell-shaped, this is oblong.
这是硕士袍
This is a master's gown.
所有人都是知道你有博士学位
Everyone knows you have a doctorate.
要不要我问问劳里
Would you like me to see if Laurie
是否能考虑给你订件新的吗
can look into ordering you a new one?
- 那会花掉我多少钱呢 - 系里出钱
- How much is that gonna run me? - Oh, on the house.
真的吗
Really?
- 我们之间的秘密 - 谢谢你
- Our secret. - Well, thanks, kiddo.
你给雅兹写的终身教职函
Um, your tenure letter for Yaz
会包含她教学的信息 对吧
is going to include material on her teaching, right?
为什么不包括呢
Why wouldn't it?
我认为你应该重点突出
I think it's important that you
她革新性的教授方法
highlight how innovative her pedagogy is.
翻转课堂
The flipped classroom...
我相信这将作为一个案例
Well, I believe a specimen of that
展现在当今的研讨会上
will be on display in today's seminar.
所以你能不能提一下它
Could you maybe include a mention of it?
听着 她现在太有人气了
Look, she is hot shit right now.
她的推特账号上有八千多的关注者
She has over 8,000 followers on Twitter.
这比我们加起来都要多
That's more than all of us put together.
你知道谁会根据自己的跟随者来判断自己吗
You know who judged himself by the number of his followers?
吉姆・琼斯  大卫・考雷什
Jim Jones. David Koresh.
雅兹不是狂热宗教的领袖 埃利奥特
Yaz isn't a cult leader, Elliot.
美国人民圣殿教的创始人和领袖
美国大卫教派教主
耶稣只有十二个跟随者 我想他只是个失败者
Jesus only had 12 followers. I suppose that makes him a loser.
因为她
Because of her,
我们的学生都对一百五十年前创作的文学作品
our students are excited
感到热血沸腾了
about literature that was written 150 years ago.
我知道在你人气火爆的时候
I know in your heyday...
你怎么知道现在不是我人气火爆的时候呢
How do you know right now is not my heyday?
听着 我不想摆架子
Look, I don't want to pull rank here,
但是作为主任 我需要你这么做
but as the chair, I need you to do this.
你肯定已经进入角色了
You sure settled into that role.
不是作为你的上司这么讲话
Not saying this as your supervisor.
- 上司 - 这是对我们系来说最好的方式
- Supervisor? - It's the best thing for the department.
对雅兹来说这也是最好的方式
And the right thing to do for Yaz,
所以你做就行了
so just do it.
没问题
随时
我想我可能发现了什么
计划是什么
明天下午五点在人文图书馆见面
我们需要伪装一下吗
你仍然有不错的身材
You still got a top-notch rear end.
希望我也能对你说这句话
Wish I could say the same for you.
鲸鱼代表了什么
What does the whale represent?
加尔文主义
Calvinism?
- 不对 是资本主义 - 白人
- No, capitalism. - Whiteness.
白人至上
White supremacy.
再说点
Say more.
"挤 挤 挤"
"Squeeze! Squeeze! Squeeze!"
"整个上午 我都在捏鲸油
"All the morning long, I squeezed that sperm
捏得我自己也差不多溶化在它里头"
till I myself almost melted into it."
"我捏着那些鲸油
"I squeezed that sperm
直捏得我竟奇奇怪怪地神志不清起来"
till a strange sort of insanity came over me."
# 以实玛利，魁魁格，弗拉斯克和斯塔布 #
Ishmael, Queequeg, Flask and Stubber
# 航行太平洋 寻找鲸油 #
Sailing the Pacific. And searching for blubber
# 塔斯蒂哥和大个儿 来把鲸鱼杀 #
Tashtego kills whales, so does Daggoo
# 整个团队只有 船员和鱼叉 #
Mates and harpooners. All part of the crew
# 布金顿的死 伴随荣光 #
Bulkington gone in a blaze of glory
# 费达拉到来 延续辉煌 #
Fedallah arrives. In the middle of the story
# 亚哈船长 日渐狂化 #
Captain Ahab goin' neurotic
# 共捏鲸油 仿若润滑 友情竟产生变化 #
While the crew's squeezin' sperm. All homoerotic
# 船上男人当互助 无须女人帮 #
No women on board. No women on board
# 绳索全剪断 #
Oh, cut the cord
# 无须女人帮 #
No women on board
# 裴廓德外 事态更甚 #
Off the Pequod. Things are grim
# 文学运动 也是男人管 #
A literary movement controlled by men
# 若要参加 先把裤子穿 #
Can only get in. If you're wearing the pants
# 文艺复兴在美国 可也需要女人帮 #
Ain't no ladies. In the American Renaissance
# 无须女人帮 #
No women on board
# 绳索全剪断 #
Cut the cord
# 无须女人帮 #
No women on board
"让你觉得我欣赏希特勒 我很抱歉
"I am sorry I made you think I like Hitler,
因为我并不欣赏他"
because I do not."
"我完全清楚 他是遗臭万年的大坏蛋"
"I know he is the worst person who ever lived."
该你了
Your turn.
"亲爱的亚丁
"Dear Adin,
我为我咬你的行为 向你表达诚挚的歉意
I want you to know how sorry I am for biting you."
"我知道咬人是不对的
"I understand that biting is never allowed,
就算是别人主动要求的"
even if the person asks."
"你是我的朋友
"You are my friend, and
我们以前常在休息时一起玩"
we used to like playing together at recess."
并没有
That's a lie.
"署名 金珠姬"
"Signed, Ju-Hee Kim."
改成"珠珠"
Put "Ju Ju."
我喜欢珠姬
I like Ju-Hee.
这是你外婆的名字 你知道的吧
It was your grandmother's name. You know that, right?
但是我不喜欢
I don't like it!
好吧 我倒觉得这个名字很美
Well, I... I think it's beautiful.
你妈妈用她的妈妈的名字给你取名 这很酷啊
Your mom named you after her mom. That's pretty cool.
这是相当大的荣誉
Pretty big honor.
通过你 让她的妈妈的生命延续下去
It's a way of keeping her mom alive, through you.
你知道"后裔"是什么意思吗
You know what "Posterity" Is?
这跟你的屁股有什么关系
Does it have to do with your butt?
屁股是"后臀"
That is "Posterior,"
发音很相似
and it's very close.
出资人想要立即开始宣传
They wanna start marketing right away.
惠滕登选了这张
Whittenden picked this.
看来我们是请他来卖干邑白兰地的
Apparently, we're hiring him to sell cognac?
呃 她想让你马上着手进行
Mmm. And she thought that you should get started right away.
半路抢了特聘讲师这个职位
It's one thing for her
是她的事
to hijack the Distinguished Lectureship,
可别想让我读大卫写的这些玩意儿
quite another to actually expect me to read these.
大卫临危受命 同意接手比尔的课程
And David has graciously agreed to take over Bill's class.
- 什么 - 只负责到听证会之前
- What? - Just until the hearing,
然后我们再看看怎么处理
and then we'll see what happens.
比尔在写致歉声明了 这件事很快就会过去
He's writing an apology. This is all going to resolve itself.
大卫需要比尔的教学大纲和讲义
David will need Bill's syllabus, lecture notes.
等等
Wait, wait, wait.
这是他特别提出的要求
He specifically asked for
为了衔接好比尔中断的地方
them so he could pick up where Bill left off.
省略掉纳粹手势
Minus the Sieg Heil.
比尔不可能交出他的讲义
Bill's not just gonna hand over his notes.
你休产假的时候可是把整个班都交出去了
When you were on maternity leave, you passed on your class...
- 那不一样 - 怎么不一样
- That is different. - How?
大卫愿意在紧要关头代课
David is willing to pinch hit for Bill.
比尔应该感激大卫对学生负责
He should be grateful that he wants to do the class justice.
比尔可不会这么想
Bill's not gonna see it that way.
比尔确实曾经受学生的欢迎
Bill was a popular teacher.
- 但是我们要 - 等下 "曾经"
- But we need to be... - Wait, "Was"?
我想给你提个建议
Can I give you a piece of advice?
你要更认真地对待你的角色
You need to start taking your role here more seriously.
你是系主任
You are chair of the department now.
不是他们的同事
You're not a peer.
明白我的意思吗
Do you get what I'm saying?
你不是比尔的同事
You are not Bill's peer.
我明天什么时候过来
What time you want me back tomorrow?
噢 不用 没事的
Oh no, that's okay.
我可能要 再找个专门的保姆
I probably should, you know, find a real babysitter.
行啦 让我来吧
Oh, come on, let me do it.
和她待在一起可以保持我的教学感
Being with her makes me, um... I don't have to miss teaching.
我要给她讲贝克特和自杀
I was gonna give her my Beckett and suicide lecture.
- 好吧 - 噢
- Okay. - Oh.
吃点像样的饭菜
This is called food.
谢谢你
Thank you.
- 我有事要跟你说 - 你怎么走了
- I have to tell you something. - Why'd you go?
你妈妈回来了 我想给她做点东西吃
Your mom came home. I wanted her to eat.
嗨 小家伙
Hi, little one.
- 你能来一下吗 - 当然可以
- Can you come? - Oh, of course.
比尔
Bill.
- 呃 让你妈妈 - 得了 去吧
- Um, don't you want your mom to... - Uh, no, go ahead.
你确定 好吧
You sure? Okay.
来吧 小机灵鬼
Come here, wise guy.
我还以为你睡着了
I thought you were asleep.
我装睡的
I was tricking you.
你能把故事讲完吗
Can you finish the story?
你知道吗
You know what it is?
她不是在教学生 而是在和他们一起玩
She doesn't wanna teach them. She wants to hang out with them.
虽然她在各大顶级刊物上发表文章 但是
Though she's publishing in all the highest venues, but...
但是什么
But what?
他们曾驳回了你的终身任职申请
They turned you down for tenure,
而你是那时最好的教授
and you were the best we had.
那时候我忙着照顾三个孩子
Because I was expected to write a book
还要写书
when I was busy raising three kids.
他们本可以让你休息一段时间
They should've stopped your tenure clock.
我本应该做更多争取
I should've put more pressure on them.
- 我很抱歉 - 都过去啦
- I'm sorry. - Shoulda, woulda.
总得有人在家做饭
Someone had to make dinner.
也对
Yeah.
- 我说过我不穿这个 - 就一晚上
- I told you I'm not wearing those. - Just tonight.
我不要穿尿布
I'm not wearing diapers.
这没什么的 只是年龄需要
This doesn't spell doom, old man.
"我曾像巨人似的跨越这狭隘的世界"
I used to bestride the narrow world like a Colossus.
现在你要穿着纸尿裤
Well, now you're going to bestride it
跨越这狭隘的世界了
in Tranquility Briefs.
老天爷啊
Oh God.
国王和王后的梦在何处"回向"
Where the dreams of kings and queens "Echoo"?
- 回响 - 回响
- Echo. - Echo.
是谁创造了卡翠娜骷髅头
Who created La Calavera Catrina?
波萨达
Posada.
- 他是在取笑谁 - 富人
- And whom was he making fun of? - Rich people.
- 什么样的富人 - 来自欧洲的
- What kind of rich people? - Ones from Europe.
你知道什么叫讽刺吗
Do you know what it means to lampoon somebody?
波萨达是在讽刺墨西哥总统波费里奥・迪亚斯
Posada was making fun of Mexican leader Porfirio Díaz
因为虽然迪亚斯完成了墨西哥的现代化改革
because even though Díaz modernized Mexico,
但是他的改革只让统治阶级获益
his reforms really only benefited the ruling class.
我也想讽刺你
I wanna lampoon you.
不 你不想
I don't think so.
我是比尔 我超无趣
My name's Bill, and I'm so boring.
珠珠 你是负责介绍墨西哥亡灵节的文化大使
Ju Ju, you're the cultural ambassador of Dia de los Muertos.
不好好准备你的报告 你会后悔的
If we don't work on your presentation, you're gonna be sorry.
我要休息
When's recess?
是我
It's me.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
我已经连上无线网络了
Um, okay, so I'm all set up on the Wi-Fi.
万事俱备 只等他发帖
Now we just, um, wait for a post.
你在读乔叟
You're reading Chaucer?
是啊 虽然我完全像在读外语
Yeah. It's like reading a different language, though, you know.
你很快就会习惯的
You'll be surprised how fast you get used to it.
只要你放空自己 放弃理解
If you can just let go and stop trying to understand...
和我写代码的时候一样
Yeah, that's how code was for me.
放任它们洗刷我的大脑
I just let it go, let it wash over me...
- 来了 - 这么快
- It's him. - Already?
- 就是他 - 对
- It's him? - Yeah.
他在哪
Where is he?
"这个丑八怪让我想自杀"
"This hag makes me wanna kill myself."
很好 你的死期已到
Good. Now it'll look like a suicide.
让我查下IP地址
Let me, uh, check the IP address.
找到了 就是他 很好
He's here. He's here. Okay.
接下来怎么...办
All right, what should we... do?
好吧
Oh, okay.
什么 不
What? No.
我复印不了资料
Well, I can't make copies,
还把我的车解锁了
but I think I just unlocked my car.
- 需要帮忙吗 - 欢迎至极
- You want a hand? - Be my guest.
- 这机器有自己的想法 - 别提了
- She's got a mind of her own. - Mmm. Don't remind me.
行了
Okay.
好极了 谢谢
Brilliant. Thank you.
不用
Yeah.
你知道梅尔维尔去世的时候
You know when Melville died,
《纽约时报》只发表了一条短短的死亡通告吗
the Times just published a tiny death notice?
他们还把《白鲸记》拼错了
They actually misspelled the title of Moby-Dick.
- 拼成了mobie - ie结尾
- m-o-b-I-e. - I-e.
- 这让我很难过 - 我也是
- It upsets me. - Well, that makes two of us.
- 谢谢 - 没事
- Thanks. - Yeah.
嘿 你忘了拿这个...
Oh, hey, you forgot your, uh...
这是一个水气球
This is a water balloon.
为了探究空气阻力和物理
In order to explore air resistance and physics,
你得接住它
what you do is you catch it.
接得好 太棒了 真是厉害...
Oh, good catch! That was perfect! That was so awes...
你这个小...
You li...
你逼我的
That's it!
你要完蛋了
You're a goner.
我来了 我来抓你了
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
你要去哪
Hey, where are you going?
珠珠 来 回来
Ju Ju, come on, come back.
我们去给妈妈一个惊喜吧
Let's go surprise Mommy!
我不能 我不可以进入校园范围内
I can't. I'm not allowed to be on campus.
干嘛啊
What the fuck?
新规 图书馆内禁止睡觉
No sleeping in the library. It's a new rule.
好吧
Oh okay.
嘿 计划是什么
Hey. So, what's the plan?
什么...
Wha...
喂
Hey.
喂 叫你呢
Hey, you!
就是他吗
Is that him?
等等 该死
Wait! Goddamn it.
等等我 等等
Wait. Wait!
快点
Come on!
嘿
Hey!
- 史蒂夫 - 汉布林教授
- Steve. - Professor Hambling?
你给我听好了
Now you listen to me.
你不喜欢我没关系
I may not be your cup of tea,
但是《坎特伯雷故事集》是一部天才之作
but The Canterbury Tales is a work of genius.
沾花惹草的丈夫 水性杨花的家庭主妇
Philandering husbands, horny housewives,
放屁 拉屎 阴毛
farting, shitting, pubic hair.
可怜的傻子向女人求吻
Some poor schmuck asked a woman for a kiss
最后走了她的后门
and ends up making out with her butthole.
我也希望你有那么好运
That's a fate I'm wishing for you.
- 差不多得了 - 你最好把那小嘴撅起来
- Okay, okay. - So, you know, pucker up.
你听清楚她说的话了吗
You hear what she's saying?
你可以不喜欢我
You don't have to like me.
但是六百多年的文学批评
But Chaucer has survived
都没能把乔叟打倒
more than 600 years of literary criticism.
要是你这都搞不懂乔叟有多牛逼
And if you can't figure out that he's a badass,
那请你别来上我的课了
then just stay the fuck out of my classroom.
帅呆了
Dope City!
你下学期教什么
What are you teaching next semester?
乔叟
Chaucer.
David Duchovny
特聘讲师
我会让他撤回的
I'll ask him to pull back.
这只是草稿
It's just a draft.
他复印的是信头纸
He was making photocopies on letterhead.
显然他是要寄出去的
Pretty sure he's ready to send it.
我绝对不会让他这么做
I promise I won't let him.
怎么了
What?
你有终身教职 我没有
You have tenure, I don't.
现在你还是系主任 我...
Now you're the chair too. I...
我也不知道 就是
I don't know, I just, I'm not
我不知道哪些话该说 哪些不该说
sure what's okay to say and what's not okay.
雅兹 如果我之前没有说清楚
Yaz, if I haven't made it clear
我希望你畅所欲言 那么...
that I want you to speak your mind, then...
那我...这是我的严重失误
Then I... I consider that a serious failure on my part.
那让我很难受
I mean, that kills me.
好吧
Okay.
这是什么意思
What are you doing?
这和你的任务有哪门子关系
How does this align with your mission?
我还以为不会再有这些破事了
I thought we moved beyond this bullshit.
我对大卫・杜楚尼这件事让步
I am giving them David Duchovny,
他们就会对你的事让步
so they will give me you.
你不该帮大卫・杜楚尼
You shouldn't be pimping for David Duchovny.
我知道...
I know...
也不该由我站出来...
I shouldn't be asked to stand out...
我在努力了
I am trying.
我丝毫没有接管了英文系的感觉
I don't feel like I inherited an English Department.
我觉得有人把一个定时炸弹扔给了我
I feel like someone handed me a ticking time bomb
因为他们想要确保 炸弹爆炸时
because they wanted to make sure a woman
责任在一个女人身上
was holding it when it explodes.
比尔和我差不多是同一时间开始在这里教书的
Bill and I started teaching here around the same time.
每次埃利奥特和我们碰上
Whenever Elliot would bump into us,
他都会拍拍比尔的背 邀请他去家里吃晚饭
he would clap Bill on the back and invite him over for dinner,
就像当我不存在一样
and I was like, "Um, hello?"
底线是 他手中依然有很多制度权力
The bottom line is, he still has a lot of institutional power.
他没有安全感 是因为没人上他的课了
He's insecure because no one takes his classes anymore.
没错
Yeah.
不 我明白你为什么同情他
No, I see why you feel sorry for him.
他统治这个行业的时间只有过去四十年而已
He only got to rule the profession for the last 40 years.
雅兹...
Yaz...
珠珠
Ju Ju!
我是认真的
I'm serious.
珠珠
Ju Ju?
等等 这已经属于校园范畴了 我不能进去
Wait. That is technically campus. I cannot be there.
不 珠珠 求你了
No, Ju Ju, please.
停下
Stop!
我不能来这里 我不能进来学校
I can't be here! I can't be on campus!
喂 多布森
Hey, Dobson.
别认输啊
Don't back down.
美国有言论自由
Free speech in America.
多布森博士
我的天 你吓死我了 你怎么在这
Oh my God, you scared me. What are you doing here?
- 我得... - 你不能进来学校的
- Uh, I gotta... - You're not supposed to be on campus.
这些是我的讲义吧
Those are my lecture notes.
是的 我...
Yes, I...
好吧 你一定要冷静
Okay, please don't freak out.
拉森让大卫・杜楚尼代你的课
Larson asked David Duchovny to teach your class.
- 什么 - 作为客座讲师
- What? - As, like, a... A guest lecturer.
只是上几节课而已
Just a few classes
只要...上到你的听证会就结束了
while we... Just until your hearing.
所以你要把讲义带回家 然后呢
So you were gonna take 'em home and then what?
邀请他过来参加研讨会吗
Invite him over for a... A seminar?
应该是我去他家 他有一栋乡村别墅...
I'm supposed to go to his house. He has a country house...
真是见了鬼了 真的要这样吗
Jesus fucking Christ. Is this really happening?
你从我这里偷讲义
You're taking my stolen notes
然后送到大卫・杜楚尼家里去
to David Duchovny's house?
不可能 这是我的知识财产
No. That's my intellectual property.
我要拿你的讲义 因为你的课必须有人来上
I am taking your notes because someone has to teach your class,
哪怕那个人是该死的大卫・杜楚尼
even if that someone is David fucking Duchovny.
更大的问题 你努力在忽略的问题
The larger issue, the one you're trying to blow by,
是你哪都能去 就是不能来...
is that you're allowed everywhere except...
珠珠呢
Where's Ju Ju?
- 珠珠 - 快去
- Oh. Ju Ju? - Go.
珠珠
Ju Ju!
- 嗨 - 亲爱的 你在干什么
- Hi! - Sweetie, what are you doing?
看着我们 别动
Look at us. Stop.
千万不要动 不 宝贝 看着我
Stop moving. No, honey, look at me.
我想跳到比尔身上
I wanna jump, to Bill.
- 面向我 - 那样可不好
- Turn to me. - That's not a good idea.
- 一 - 好吧
- One. - Okay.
- 好吧 来吧 - 二
- Okay, okay. - Two.
- 等等 先别 天啊 - 三
- Hold on. Hold on. Oh God! - Three!
没事了
Oh God.
- 你吓到妈妈了 - 好了 我们走吧
- You scared your mama. - Okay, let's go.
- 走吧... - 你吓坏妈妈了
- Let's... - You scared your mama.
- 宝贝 走吧 - 停下 不要
- Sweetheart, let's go. - Stop it. No.
- 比尔能来吗 - 不行
- Can Bill come? - No.
- 今晚不行 - 不 我们得走了
- Not tonight. - No, we gotta leave.
- 过来吃晚饭 - 不行 宝贝
- Come for dinner. - No, sweetheart.
- 来嘛 - 我们真的得走了
- Come! - We have got to leave.
- 来嘛 - 好了 先上车
- Come on! - Okay, to the car.
- 妈妈 - 上车吧
- Mom! - To the car?
- 好 - 上车
- Yes. - To the car?
妈妈 你好矮哦
Mommy, you're so short.
也很可爱
And cute.
好了好了
Okay. Yeah.
你来吧 比尔
You do it, Bill.